Guide to the Small Towns Institute Records 1956-2002 (bulk 1969-1997)
Central Washington University Archives and Special Collections
- Organization files, 1969-1998; III
  - Concerned Citizens for the Hudson Valley, 1968-1971 (Box-folder 87-9)
  - Congressional Rural Caucus, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 87-10)
  - Connecticut Humanities Council, 1984 (Box-folder 87-11)
  - Connecticut Trust for Historic Preservation, 1981 (Box-folder 87-12)
  - Council on Development Choices for the 80s, 1980 (Box-folder 87-13)
  - Council for Planning Libraries, 1978 (Box-folder 87-14)
  - Council of State Governments, 1989 (Box-folder 87-15)
  - Design for Clark County, 1970-1971 (Box-folder 87-16)
  - Design Michigan, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 88-1)
  - Downtown Research and Development Center, 1978-1991 (Box-folder 88-2)
  - Downtown Research and Development Center, 1978-1991 (Box-folder 88-3)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 88-4)
  - Environmental Protection Agency, 1973-1986 (Box-folder 88-5)
  - Environmentalists for Full Employment, 1976-1978 (Box-folder 88-6)
  - ERIC Clearing House on Rural Education and Small Schools, 1971-1990 (Box-folder 88-7)
  - Expo ’86, Vancouver, British Columbia, 1985-1986 (Box-folder 88-8)
  - Federal Energy Administration, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 88-9)
  - Federation of Canadian Municipalities, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 88-10)
  - Federation of Southern Cooperatives, 1972 (Box-folder 88-11)
  - Friends of the Earth, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 89-1)
  - Georgia Endowment for the Humanities, 1983 (Box-folder 89-2)
  - Glenmary Research Center, 1987 (Box-folder 89-3)
  - Grange, 1970 (Box-folder 89-4)
  - Gunlogson, G. B., 1976-1988 (Box-folder 89-5)
  - Gunlogson, G. B., 1976-1988 (Box-folder 89-6)
  - Gunlogson, G. B., 1976-1988 (Box-folder 89-7)
  - Heartland Center for Leadership Development, 1990 (Box-folder 89-8)
  - Heritage Canada, 1984 (Box-folder 89-9)
  - Heritage Conservation and Recreation Services, 1981 (Box-folder 89-10)
  - Historic House Association of America, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 90-1)
  - Historic Landmarks of Indiana, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 90-2)
  - Historic Landmarks of Indiana, 1985-1990 (Box-folder 90-3)
  - Historic New Harmony Inc., 1979 (Box-folder 90-4)
  - Historic Preservation Society of North Carolina, 1982-1985 (Box-folder 90-5)
  - House Assistance Council, 1973-1979 (Box-folder 90-6)
  - Idaho Assistance for the Humanities, 1983 (Box-folder 90-7)
  - IDEA (International Downtown Executives Association), 1981-1984 (Box-folder 90-8)
  - Indiana Committee for the Humanities, 1984 (Box-folder 90-9)
  - Institute for the Community Economics Program and Accomplishments, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 90-10)
  - Institute of Cultural Affairs, 1981-1983 (Box-folder 90-11)
  - Institute for Local Self-Reliance, 1976-1981 (Box-folder 90-12)
  - Institute for Urban Design, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 90-13)
  - Institute of Science and Man, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 91-1)
  - Institute of Science and Man, 1972-1986 (Box-folder 91-2)
  - Institute for Research on Poverty (Box-folder 91-3)
  - International City Management Association, 1978-1980 (Box-folder 91-4)
  - International Independent Institute, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 91-5)
  - Institute for Policy Studies, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 91-6)
  - International Council of Shopping Centers, 1984 (Box-folder 91-7)
  - International Institute of Municipal Clerks, 1977-1983 (Box-folder 91-8)
  - International Telephone and Telegraph Corporation, 1973 (Box-folder 91-9)
  - Iowa Humanities Board, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 91-10)
  - Junior Chamber of Commerce, 1977-1978 (Box-folder 91-11)
  - Kentucky Humanities Council, 1983-1987 (Box-folder 91-12)
  - Kansas Committee for the Humanities, 1974-1983 (Box-folder 91-13)
  - Keep America Beautiful Inc., 1983-1984 (Box-folder 91-14)
  - Landmarks Preservation Council of Illinois, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 91-15)
  - League of Historic American Theaters, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 91-16)
  - Louisiana Committee for the Humanities, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 92-1)
  - Maine Coast Heritage Trust (Box-folder 92-2)
  - Maine Humanities Council, 1982 (Box-folder 92-3)
  - Maryland Humanities Council, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 92-4)
  - Massachusetts Foundation for Humanities, 1983-1984 (Box-folder 92-5)
  - Metro, 1976-1980 (Box-folder 92-6)
  - Michigan Council for the Humanities, 1984 (Box-folder 92-7)
  - Michigan State University – School of Labor, 1972 (Box-folder 92-8)
  - Michigan Society of Planning Officials, 1983 (Box-folder 92-9)
  - Midwest Living Magazine, 1987 (Box-folder 92-10)
  - Minnesota Humanities Commission, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 92-11)
  - Mississippi Center for Small Town Design, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 92-12)
  - Mississippi Committee for the Humanities, 1982-1984 (Box-folder 92-13)
  - Montana Committee for the Humanities, 1984 (Box-folder 92-14)
  - Municipal Officer’s Association of British Columbia, 1985-1987 (Box-folder 92-15)
  - NAHRO (National Association of Housing and Redevelopment Officials), 1979-1981 (Box-folder 92-16)
  - National Area Development Institute (Box-folder 92-17)
  - National Association of Counties, 1972 (Box-folder 92-18)
  - National Association of Counties, 1982 (Box-folder 92-19)
  - National Association of Development Organizations, 1985 (Box-folder 92-20)
  - National Association of Regional Councils, 1984 (Box-folder 92-21)
  - National Association of State Development Agencies, 1983 (Box-folder 92-22)
  - National Association of Towns And Township Officials, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 93-1)
  - National Center for Employee Ownership (Box-folder 93-2)
  - National Council for the Traditional Arts, 1981 (Box-folder 93-3)
  - National Endowment for the Arts, 1984 (Box-folder 93-4)
  - National Endowment for the Humanities, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 93-5)
  - National Land for People, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 93-6)
  - National League of Cities, 1985 (Box-folder 93-7)
  - National League of Cities – Environment Design Project, 1980 (Box-folder 93-8)
  - National Municipal League, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 93-9)
  - National Recreation and Parks Association, 1983 (Box-folder 93-10)
  - National Rural Center, 1978-1985 (Box-folder 93-11)
  - National Rural Fellows, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 93-12)
  - National Science Foundation, 1976-1979 (Box-folder 93-13)
  - Natural Disaster Recovery and Migration Resource Referral Service, 1982 (Box-folder 93-14)
  - NEAPQ Center – University of Maine, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 93-15)
  - Nebraska Committee for the Humanities, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 93-16)
  - Neighborhood Arts Programs National Organization Committee, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 93-17)
  - Nevada Humanities Council, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 94-1)
  - New England Resource Agency Information Exchange, 1978-1981 (Box-folder 94-2)
  - Newfoundland and Labrador Federation of Municipalities, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 94-3)
  - New Hampshire Association of Conservation Committee, 1975 (Box-folder 94-4)
  - New Jersey Committees for the Humanities, 1984 (Box-folder 94-5)
  - New York State Commission on Rural Resources, 1983 (Box-folder 94-6)
  - North Carolina Humanities Committee, 1984-1985 (Box-folder 94-7)
  - Northeast-Midwest Congressional Coalition, 1984 (Box-folder 94-8)
  - Northeastern Iowa Human Resource Center, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 94-9)
  - Northwest Power Planning Council, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 94-10)
  - Northwest Power Planning Council, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 94-11)
  - Northwest Power Planning Council, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 94-12)
  - Ohio Humanities Council, 1984-1988 (Box-folder 94-13)
  - Ohio Planning Conference, 1973-1981 (Box-folder 95-1)
  - Oklahoma Foundation for the Humanities, 1985 (Box-folder 95-2)
  - Ontario Association of Architects, 1984 (Box-folder 95-3)
  - Ontario Organization of Small Urban Municipalities, 1982 (Box-folder 95-4)
  - Pacific Northwest Ballet Association, 1972 (Box-folder 95-5)
  - Partners for Livable Places, 1981-1988 (Box-folder 95-6)
  - Partnerships for Rural Improvement, 1978-1982 (Box-folder 95-7)
  - Pennsylvania Planning Association, 1984 (Box-folder 95-8)
  - People, Food and Land, 1986 (Box-folder 95-9)
  - Pioneer America Society, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 95-10)
  - Pioneer America Society, 1971-1974 (Box-folder 95-11)
  - Planning Association of Washington, 1972-1982 (Box-folder 96-1)
  - Preservation League of New York State, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 96-2)
  - President’s Commission on the American Outdoors, 1976 (Box-folder 96-3)
  - President’s Commission on the American Outdoors, 1986 (Box-folder 96-4)
  - Private Revitalization of Downtown – Santa Cruz, California, 1976 (Box-folder 96-5)
  - Project for Public Spaces, 1979 (Box-folder 96-6)
  - Project Green – Iowa City, Iowa, 1973-1977 (Box-folder 96-7)
  - Public Administration Institute of Canada, 1982 (Box-folder 96-8)
  - Public and Private Ventures, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 96-9)
  - Public and Private Ventures, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 96-10)
  - Public and Private Ventures, 1983-1995 (Box-folder 96-11)
  - Puget Sound Government Conference, 1983 (Box-folder 96-12)
  - Ruby Arts of Lake Chelan, 1974 (Box-folder 96-13)
  - Rural America, 1977 (Box-folder 97-1)
  - Rural Coalition, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 97-2)
  - Rural Development Outreach Program Center, 1979-1980 (Box-folder 97-3)
  - Rural Education Association, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 97-4)
  - “Rural Opportunities", 1968-1969 (Box-folder 97-5)
  - Science, Mathematics and Environment Education Information Analysis Center, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 97-6)
  - Smithsonian Science Information Exchange - Newsletter, 1978-1979 (Box-folder 97-7)
  - Social Science Research Center, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 97-8)
  - Southern Rural Development Center, 1976-1982 (Box-folder 97-9)
  - Southwest Research and Information Center, 1974 (Box-folder 97-10)
  - Southwest State University, 1978 (Box-folder 97-11)
  - State of Washington Planning and Community Affairs Department of Community Development, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 97-12)
  - Team 4, 1977-1980 (Box-folder 97-13)
  - Texas Committee for the Humanities, 1984 (Box-folder 97-14)
  - “Tilth" - Newsletter, 1975-1979 (Box-folder 97-15)
  - Townscape Institute, 1972-1977 (Box-folder 97-16)
  - “Tranet" - Newsletter, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 98-1)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1977-1992 (Box-folder 98-2)
  - Tennessee Valley Authority, 1977-1992 (Box-folder 98-3)
  - United States Department of Agriculture, 1972-1980 (Box-folder 98-4)
  - “Urban Design" – Newsletter, 1974-1981 (Box-folder 98-5)
  - Urban Land Institute, 1986 (Box-folder 98-6)
  - Vermont Natural Resources Forum, 1973-1976 (Box-folder 98-7)
  - “Victorian Homes" – Journal, 1982 (Box-folder 98-8)
  - Vision 17, 1970 (Box-folder 98-9)
  - W. E. Upjohn Institute for Employment Research, 1983 (Box-folder 98-10)
  - Waccama Regional Planning and Development, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 98-11)
  - Washington Commission for the Humanities, 1980-1985 (Box-folder 98-12)
  - Washington State Task Force on Rural Affairs, 1971 (Box-folder 98-13)
  - Washington Trust for Historic Preservation, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 98-14)
  - Washington Trust for Historic Preservation, 1979-1987 (Box-folder 99-1)
  - Waste Management Professionals Association, 1985 (Box-folder 99-2)
  - Waterford Foundation, 1981-1982 (Box-folder 99-3)
  - Waterfront Center, 1982-1983 (Box-folder 99-4)
  - Western Interstate Commission for Higher Education, 1973 (Box-folder 99-5)
  - Western States Arts Foundation, 1984 (Box-folder 99-6)
  - White House Task Force on Small Towns, 1973 (Box-folder 99-7)
  - Whitman County Regional Planning Council, 1979-1981 (Box-folder 99-8)
  - Wisconsin Humanities Committee, 1984 (Box-folder 99-9)
  - Wyoming Council for the Humanities, 1984 (Box-folder 99-10)
  - Zero Population Growth, 1976 (Box-folder 99-11)
- Article submissions and drafts, 1966-2002; IV
  This series contains correspondence, photographs and drafts of articles submitted for publication and published in the Small Town Institute’s journal from 1966 to 2002. This series is organized alphabetically by surname of the author.
  - Alabama Planning Community “WeissLake" (Box-folder 100-1)
  - Allen, David – Catfish Farming, 1989 (Box-folder 100-2)
  - Arnold, David – Children and Sidewalks, 1988 (Box-folder 100-3)
  - Aspaas, Helen Ruth – Women’s Home Based Business, 1966-1967 (Box-folder 100-4)
  - Atash, Farhand – Multimodal Transportation Strategies, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 100-5)
  - Ayers, James R. – Terracing Farmland, 1990 (Box-folder 100-6)
  - Ballard, Chester C. – Oil Boom Town, 1982 (Box-folder 100-7)
  - Barnes, Stephen H. – Rural Fine Arts Colleges, 1988 (Box-folder 100-8)
  - Barlett, Sheridan – Brattleboro, Vermont, 1990 (Box-folder 100-9)
  - Becker, Jay – Community Newsletter, 1999 (Box-folder 100-10)
  - Becker, Jay – Former Social Worker, Man and Pop Farmers, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 100-11)
  - Becker, Jay – Great Plains Remote Town, 1999 (Box-folder 100-12)
  - Belits, Catherine A. – Farmland Preservation, 1989 (Box-folder 100-13)
  - Belknap, Larry K. – Leisure Activities for Women, 1989 (Box-folder 100-14)
  - Benhart, John E. – Interstate 81 Corridor, 1992 (Box-folder 100-15)
  - Benhart, John E. – Planning and Regional Development, 1996 (Box-folder 100-16)
  - Bernlin, Robert – Earthquake Hazards, 1986 (Box-folder 100-17)
  - Betz, Melanie – Preserving County Courthouses, 1985 (Box-folder 100-18)
  - Blevins, Andre / Hong, Dan – Laramie, Wyoming, 1993 (Box-folder 100-19)
  - Blisard, Herb – Matter of Scale, 1992 (Box-folder 100-20)
  - Bloom, Alice – Mt. Vernon, Maine, 1991 (Box-folder 100-21)
  - Boulger, James C. – Small Town Medical Practice, 1982 (Box-folder 100-22)
  - Bourke, Lisa – Case of Bedford, 1995 (Box-folder 101-1)
  - Bowling, Michael – Illinois Rural Tourism, 1992 (Box-folder 101-2)
  - Boyd, Sheryl – Youth Helping Seniors, 1989 (Box-folder 101-3)
  - Bradbury, S. L. – Communities in Transition, 1997 (Box-folder 101-4)
  - Bradbury, S. L. – Expanding the Tourist Season, 1994 (Box-folder 101-5)
  - Bradbury, S. L. – Planning without a Planner, 1991 (Box-folder 101-6)
  - Bradford, Janet K. – Santa Luisa, California, Earthquake, 1984 (Box-folder 101-7)
  - Branch, Kenneth J. – Consolidating the Village School, 1987 (Box-folder 101-8)
  - Break, Helen – Ontario’s Rural Service Areas, 1988 (Box-folder 101-9)
  - Bright, Robert D. – How’s your Organization, 1987 (Box-folder 101-10)
  - Brighton, Deborah – Fostering Commercial Development, 1991 (Box-folder 101-11)
  - Broadway, Michael – What Happens when the Meat Packers come to Town, 1994 (Box-folder 101-12)
  - Brookings, Oregon – Recreation, Parks and Leisure (Box-folder 101-13)
  - Brooks, Rusty – Georgia Downtowns, 1995 (Box-folder 101-14)
  - Brown, Bridget – Academy Village, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 101-15)
  - Brown, Dennis M. – The State of Transportation in America, 1996 (Box-folder 101-16)
  - Brown, Dennis M. – Public Transportation, 1988 (Box-folder 101-17)
  - Brown-Manrique, Gerardo – Design Guidelines as Controls on Environment, 1991 (Box-folder 101-18)
  - Buchanan, Gary – Import Replacement, 1995 (Box-folder 101-19)
  - Carlson, David A. – Role of Church in Farm Disputes, 1989 (Box-folder 101-20)
  - Caruso, Christopher – Open Space, 1996 (Box-folder 101-21)
  - Carter, Emanuel – Ways of Looking at Community, 1990 (Box-folder 101-22)
  - Caudillo, Nancy Lauts – Illinois Economic Development, 1991 (Box-folder 102-1)
  - Caudle, Mildred W. – Pulaski, Tennessee, 1988 (Box-folder 102-2)
  - Chabot, Robert – Net Retail Leakage: Ohio, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 102-3)
  - Chawla, Louise – Kentucky Childhoods: 1900 to Now, 1994 (Box-folder 102-4)
  - Childress, Herb – No Loitering, 1993 (Box-folder 102-5)
  - Clements, Christine and LaNelda, Ralley – Using Public Relations to Boost Community Promotional Efforts (Box-folder 102-6)
  - Cleveland, Stepnanie and Hansen, Chris – Sedro-Woolley, Washington, 1994 (Box-folder 102-7)
  - Coe, Benjamin P. – Part-time Public Officials, 1987 (Box-folder 102-8)
  - Coffy, Brian – New York Tax Shift, 1990-1995 (Box-folder 102-9)
  - Cole, Brian D. – Baker City, Oregon, 1993 (Box-folder 102-10)
  - Costello, Anthony J. – Preservation through Local News, 1983 (Box-folder 102-11)
  - Costello, Anthony J. – Taking the Basic Steps to the Charrette Process, 1987 (Box-folder 102-12)
  - Costello, Anthony J. – Taking the Basic Steps to the Charrette Process, 1987 (Box-folder 102-13)
  - Coyle, Michael P. – Disaster Planning, 1984 (Box-folder 102-14)
  - Crankshaw, Ned – Trees and Environment of Downtown Street Corridors, 1994 (Box-folder 102-15)
  - Crankshaw, Ned – Walking Places in Small Town, 1999 (Box-folder 102-16)
  - Crihfield, John B. – Reily’s Law, 1991 (Box-folder 102-17)
  - Crush, Teresa – Thermopolis, Wyoming, Main Street, 1985 (Box-folder 102-18)
  - Curles, Lawrence J. – Port Orchard, Washington, Waterfront, 1989 (Box-folder 102-19)
  - Dahms, Frederick – Economic Revitalization, 1991 (Box-folder 102-20)
  - Daller, Timothy – Northwest Angle, Minnesota, 1997 (Box-folder 102-21)
  - Daniels, Tom N. and Keller, T. – WalMart Comes to Town, 1991 (Box-folder 102-22)
  - Davidson, Claud M. – Local Health Care in Texas, 1992 (Box-folder 103-1)
  - Davidson, Claud M. – Texas Tech University, 1990 (Box-folder 103-2)
  - DeLyser, Dydia – Ghost Towns, 1995 (Box-folder 103-3)
  - Denman, Anne S. – Iowa City (Box-folder 103-4)
  - Devine, David – Casa Granda, Arizona, 1984 (Box-folder 103-5)
  - DiGrino, Nick – Informing Citizens, 1986 (Box-folder 103-6)
  - Dillman, Don A. – Mobie Homes, 1982 (Box-folder 103-7)
  - Doherty, J. C. – Utility Locations as Plan Tool (Box-folder 103-8)
  - Doom, Ira F. – Volunteer Transportation Program, 1984 (Box-folder 103-9)
  - Downey, Maryjo – Carousel Restoration Project, 1983 (Box-folder 103-10)
  - Driskell, Jeanette – Third and Main, 1980 (Box-folder 103-11)
  - Duffy-Armstrong, Marilyn – Environmental Design, 1981 (Box-folder 103-12)
  - Edwards, James R. – Citizens of History, 1994 (Box-folder 103-13)
  - Ellis, William E. – Small Towns in Transition, 1995 (Box-folder 103-14)
  - Elmerdorf, Richard – Development Impact Fees, 1992 (Box-folder 103-15)
  - Engler, Mira – Theme Towns, 1994 (Box-folder 103-16)
  - Erickson, Carolyn – Country Store lives, 1984 (Box-folder 103-17)
  - Evangelist, Frank – Arts and Crafts in Andover, New York, 1987 (Box-folder 103-18)
  - Everitt, John C. – Tale of Two Towns, 1994 (Box-folder 103-19)
  - Farner, Jeffroy – Agricultural Preservation, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 103-20)
  - Farwell, Byron – Rural Election in Virginia (Box-folder 103-21)
  - Fast, Manfred – Communities can Make it Happen, 1995 (Box-folder 103-22)
  - Fincham, Allen G. – Alcoa, Tennessee, 1998 (Box-folder 103-23)
  - Findlay, Robert – Three Visual Imaging Techniques, 1989 (Box-folder 103-24)
  - Flaccaverto, Anthony – Values and Community Development, 1988 (Box-folder 103-25)
  - Fleming, Cory – Making More of Loess, 1993 (Box-folder 103-26)
  - Fleming, Ronald Lee – Landscape of the Mind, 1981 (Box-folder 103-27)
  - Flittie, Edwin C. – Moving from Metropolis, 1982 (Box-folder 103-28)
  - Forbes, William – A Tale of Two Diversities, 1994 (Box-folder 103-29)
  - Ford, Jack J. – Zoning Rural Highway Corridor, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 104-1)
  - Forrester, Randy – Angle Fire, New Mexico, 1990 (Box-folder 104-2)
  - Francaviglia, Richard V. – Bisbee, Arizona, 1983 (Box-folder 104-3)
  - Francaviglia, Richard V. – Evolution of Mining Scapes, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 104-4)
  - Fridlund, Paul – Fisk Photographs, 1981 (Box-folder 104-5)
  - Garnham, Harry L. – Telluride, Colorado, 1989 (Box-folder 104-6)
  - Garula, Samuel – Centralia, Pennsylvania Mine Fire, 1985 (Box-folder 104-7)
  - Gaylord, Hugh – Planning Reform in Ontario and its Implications, 1996 (Box-folder 104-8)
  - Gilman, Dennis S. – Preservation of Banker’s Row, 1985 (Box-folder 104-9)
  - Goudy, Willis – Changes in the Numbers, 1990 (Box-folder 104-10)
  - Greenburg, Gary – No title, 1994 (Box-folder 104-11)
  - Grossman, Howard J. – Town Adjusts to Budget Cuts, 1985 (Box-folder 104-12)
  - Gruidl, John and Kline, Steve – What happens when a Large Discount Store comes to Town, 1992 (Box-folder 104-13)
  - Guenther, Judith – Selling Main Street, 1983 (Box-folder 104-14)
  - Gurnee, J. Michael – Reflecting Lifestyles in Zoning, 1982 (Box-folder 104-15)
  - Hala, Natalie A. – Emerging Artists – Cataba City, North Carolina, 1987 (Box-folder 104-16)
  - Hall, Donna L. – Historic Districts of Washington State, 1991 (Box-folder 104-17)
  - Halseth, Greg – C.E.D. Groups in Non-Metro British Columbia, 1997 (Box-folder 104-18)
  - Halseth, Greg – Information Needs, 2001 (Box-folder 104-19)
  - Hankins, Robb – Artstown, U.S.A., 1986 (Box-folder 104-20)
  - Hansen, Tim – Small Town Entrances, 1984 (Box-folder 104-21)
  - Hawley, Jana – Do Retailers Plan (or Pray) for Success, 1996 (Box-folder 104-22)
  - Herr, Philip B. – Nuclear Emergency Response (Box-folder 104-23)
  - Hestekin, Kay – Providing Affordable Housing, 1991 (Box-folder 104-24)
  - Hester, Randolph T., Jr. – Inspiring Community Action, 1988 (Box-folder 104-25)
  - Hester, Randolph T., Jr. – Local Planning in Rural Towns, 1988 (Box-folder 104-26)
  - Hester, Randolph T., Jr. – Manteo, North Carolina, 1989 (Box-folder 104-27)
  - Hester, Randy – Blueprint, 1998 (Box-folder 105-1)
  - Hester, Randy – Small towns in Taiwan, 1998 (Box-folder 105-2)
  - Hines, Bob – Ashville, Ohio, 1982 (Box-folder 105-3)
  - Historic Preservation Issue – Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box-folder 105-4)
  - Honadle, Beth Walter – Using Cooperation, 1980 (Box-folder 105-5)
  - Hooey, Catherine – When an Auto Giant comes to Town, 1995 (Box-folder 105-6)
  - Hooks, Grey – Factory Closings, 1982 (Box-folder 105-7)
  - Hooper, Anthony I. – New Berne, North Carolina, 1986 (Box-folder 105-8)
  - Hoover, Janet Williams – Rural Doctors, 1986 (Box-folder 105-9)
  - Historic Preservation Issue – Miscellaneous, 1982 (Box-folder 105-10)
  - Horstman, Neil – Professionals in State Preservation, 1982 (Box-folder 105-11)
  - Houstoun, Lawrence O. – Non-Metropolitan Growth, 1981 (Box-folder 105-12)
  - Hoviner, Gary R. – Lancaster County Tourism, 1997 (Box-folder 105-13)
  - Howell, Richard (Box-folder 105-14)
  - Hudler, Adrian W. – Small Town Doctors, 1992 (Box-folder 105-15)
  - Hutchinson, John C. – Were in this Together, 1988 (Box-folder 105-16)
  - Ircha, Michael C. – Canadian Shopping Centers, 1983 (Box-folder 105-17)
  - Jenkins, Janet R. – Cliff Dwellers, 1986 (Box-folder 105-18)
  - Jensen, Katherine and Blevins, Audie – The Remaking of a Company Mining Town, 1992 (Box-folder 105-19)
  - Jensen, Katherine and Blevins, Audie – Builder, Retailer, Restorer, 1998 (Box-folder 105-20)
  - Johnson, Ann L. – Beverton, Oregon, 1987 (Box-folder 105-21)
  - Johnson, Peter C. – Land Use in Douglas County, 1995 (Box-folder 105-22)
  - Johnson, Ronald – Bed and Breakfast: Waterloo, 1992 (Box-folder 105-23)
  - Jones, Daniel R. – Landscaping Mobil Home Parks, 1983 (Box-folder 105-24)
  - Jutla, Rajinders – Visual Preferences of Townscape, 1998 (Box-folder 105-25)
  - Kanhi, Victor – Ridesharing, 1982 (Box-folder 105-26)
  - Kaprisin, Ron – Tourism in Alaska Gold Rush Town, 1982 (Box-folder 105-27)
  - Karia, Michael R. – New Towns in Far North, 1989 (Box-folder 105-28)
  - Kaye, Stephen C. – Short Trip into Open Space, 1992 (Box-folder 105-29)
  - Kazzi, John W. – Keep America Beautiful, 1990 (Box-folder 105-30)
  - Keirstead, Donna – Old Town, Financing Development, 1981 (Box-folder 105-31)
  - Kenyon, James B. – Central Social District, 1989 (Box-folder 105-32)
  - Kern, Christopher J. – Rethinking Main Street, Oswego, New York, 1993 (Box-folder 105-33)
  - Kim, Joochu – Mohave County, Arizona, Recreation, 1986 (Box-folder 106-1)
  - Kleiner, Anna M. – Achieving Multi-Community Consolidation, 1996 (Box-folder 106-2)
  - Knapp, Tim – A Bumpy Economic Road, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 106-3)